[
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 1 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 100.00%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 2 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 50.00%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 50.00%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 3 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 33.33%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 33.33%, BCC Global ETN: 33.33%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 4 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 25.00%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 25.00%, BCC Global ETN: 25.00%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 25.00%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 5 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 20.00%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 20.00%, BCC Global ETN: 20.00%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 20.00%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 20.00%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 6 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 16.67%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 16.67%, BCC Global ETN: 16.67%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 16.67%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 16.67%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 16.67%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 7 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 14.29%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 14.29%, BCC Global ETN: 14.29%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 14.29%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 14.29%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 14.29%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 14.29%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 8 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 12.50%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 12.50%, BCC Global ETN: 12.50%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 12.50%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 12.50%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 12.50%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 12.50%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 12.50%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 9 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 11.11%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 11.11%, BCC Global ETN: 11.11%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 11.11%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 11.11%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 11.11%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 11.11%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 11.11%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 11.11%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 10 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 10.00%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 10.00%, BCC Global ETN: 10.00%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 10.00%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 10.00%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 10.00%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 10.00%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 10.00%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 10.00%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 10.00%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 11 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 9.09%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 9.09%, BCC Global ETN: 9.09%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 9.09%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 9.09%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 9.09%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 9.09%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 9.09%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 9.09%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 9.09%, ICBC Credit Suisse GEM Index Investment Fund: 9.09%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 12 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 8.33%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 8.33%, BCC Global ETN: 8.33%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 8.33%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 8.33%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 8.33%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 8.33%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 8.33%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 8.33%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 8.33%, ICBC Credit Suisse GEM Index Investment Fund: 8.33%, Fullgoal CSI Tourism Thematic ETF: 8.33%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 13 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 7.69%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 7.69%, BCC Global ETN: 7.69%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 7.69%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 7.69%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 7.69%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 7.69%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 7.69%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 7.69%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 7.69%, ICBC Credit Suisse GEM Index Investment Fund: 7.69%, Fullgoal CSI Tourism Thematic ETF: 7.69%, iPath CBOE S&P 500 BuyWrite Index ETN: 7.69%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 14 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 7.14%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 7.14%, BCC Global ETN: 7.14%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 7.14%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 7.14%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 7.14%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 7.14%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 7.14%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 7.14%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 7.14%, ICBC Credit Suisse GEM Index Investment Fund: 7.14%, Fullgoal CSI Tourism Thematic ETF: 7.14%, iPath CBOE S&P 500 BuyWrite Index ETN: 7.14%, MTEK ETF Leaders Tech: 7.14%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 15 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 6.67%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 6.67%, BCC Global ETN: 6.67%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 6.67%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 6.67%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 6.67%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 6.67%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 6.67%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 6.67%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 6.67%, ICBC Credit Suisse GEM Index Investment Fund: 6.67%, Fullgoal CSI Tourism Thematic ETF: 6.67%, iPath CBOE S&P 500 BuyWrite Index ETN: 6.67%, MTEK ETF Leaders Tech: 6.67%, Hwabao WP CSI Old-Age Industry ETF: 6.67%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 16 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 6.25%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 6.25%, BCC Global ETN: 6.25%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 6.25%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 6.25%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 6.25%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 6.25%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 6.25%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 6.25%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 6.25%, ICBC Credit Suisse GEM Index Investment Fund: 6.25%, Fullgoal CSI Tourism Thematic ETF: 6.25%, iPath CBOE S&P 500 BuyWrite Index ETN: 6.25%, MTEK ETF Leaders Tech: 6.25%, Hwabao WP CSI Old-Age Industry ETF: 6.25%, Penghua CSI 800 Securities and Insurance ETF: 6.25%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 17 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 5.88%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 5.88%, BCC Global ETN: 5.88%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 5.88%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 5.88%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 5.88%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 5.88%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 5.88%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 5.88%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 5.88%, ICBC Credit Suisse GEM Index Investment Fund: 5.88%, Fullgoal CSI Tourism Thematic ETF: 5.88%, iPath CBOE S&P 500 BuyWrite Index ETN: 5.88%, MTEK ETF Leaders Tech: 5.88%, Hwabao WP CSI Old-Age Industry ETF: 5.88%, Penghua CSI 800 Securities and Insurance ETF: 5.88%, ICICI Prudential S&P BSE Liquid Rate ETF: 5.88%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 18 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 5.56%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 5.56%, BCC Global ETN: 5.56%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 5.56%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 5.56%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 5.56%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 5.56%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 5.56%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 5.56%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 5.56%, ICBC Credit Suisse GEM Index Investment Fund: 5.56%, Fullgoal CSI Tourism Thematic ETF: 5.56%, iPath CBOE S&P 500 BuyWrite Index ETN: 5.56%, MTEK ETF Leaders Tech: 5.56%, Hwabao WP CSI Old-Age Industry ETF: 5.56%, Penghua CSI 800 Securities and Insurance ETF: 5.56%, ICICI Prudential S&P BSE Liquid Rate ETF: 5.56%, Mirae Asset Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 5.56%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 19 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 5.26%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 5.26%, BCC Global ETN: 5.26%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 5.26%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 5.26%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 5.26%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 5.26%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 5.26%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 5.26%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 5.26%, ICBC Credit Suisse GEM Index Investment Fund: 5.26%, Fullgoal CSI Tourism Thematic ETF: 5.26%, iPath CBOE S&P 500 BuyWrite Index ETN: 5.26%, MTEK ETF Leaders Tech: 5.26%, Hwabao WP CSI Old-Age Industry ETF: 5.26%, Penghua CSI 800 Securities and Insurance ETF: 5.26%, ICICI Prudential S&P BSE Liquid Rate ETF: 5.26%, Mirae Asset Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 5.26%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet CPI Linked 2023: 5.26%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 20 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 5.00%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 5.00%, BCC Global ETN: 5.00%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 5.00%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 5.00%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 5.00%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 5.00%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 5.00%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 5.00%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 5.00%, ICBC Credit Suisse GEM Index Investment Fund: 5.00%, Fullgoal CSI Tourism Thematic ETF: 5.00%, iPath CBOE S&P 500 BuyWrite Index ETN: 5.00%, MTEK ETF Leaders Tech: 5.00%, Hwabao WP CSI Old-Age Industry ETF: 5.00%, Penghua CSI 800 Securities and Insurance ETF: 5.00%, ICICI Prudential S&P BSE Liquid Rate ETF: 5.00%, Mirae Asset Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 5.00%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet CPI Linked 2023: 5.00%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet Non Linked 2023: 5.00%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 21 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 4.76%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 4.76%, BCC Global ETN: 4.76%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 4.76%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 4.76%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 4.76%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 4.76%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 4.76%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 4.76%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 4.76%, ICBC Credit Suisse GEM Index Investment Fund: 4.76%, Fullgoal CSI Tourism Thematic ETF: 4.76%, iPath CBOE S&P 500 BuyWrite Index ETN: 4.76%, MTEK ETF Leaders Tech: 4.76%, Hwabao WP CSI Old-Age Industry ETF: 4.76%, Penghua CSI 800 Securities and Insurance ETF: 4.76%, ICICI Prudential S&P BSE Liquid Rate ETF: 4.76%, Mirae Asset Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 4.76%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet CPI Linked 2023: 4.76%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet Non Linked 2023: 4.76%, Yuanta TPEx ESG Growth ETN: 4.76%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 22 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 4.55%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 4.55%, BCC Global ETN: 4.55%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 4.55%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 4.55%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 4.55%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 4.55%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 4.55%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 4.55%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 4.55%, ICBC Credit Suisse GEM Index Investment Fund: 4.55%, Fullgoal CSI Tourism Thematic ETF: 4.55%, iPath CBOE S&P 500 BuyWrite Index ETN: 4.55%, MTEK ETF Leaders Tech: 4.55%, Hwabao WP CSI Old-Age Industry ETF: 4.55%, Penghua CSI 800 Securities and Insurance ETF: 4.55%, ICICI Prudential S&P BSE Liquid Rate ETF: 4.55%, Mirae Asset Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 4.55%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet CPI Linked 2023: 4.55%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet Non Linked 2023: 4.55%, Yuanta TPEx ESG Growth ETN: 4.55%, UBS ETC on UBS Bloomberg CMCI Agriculture TR Index CHF: 4.55%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 23 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 4.35%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 4.35%, BCC Global ETN: 4.35%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 4.35%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 4.35%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 4.35%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 4.35%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 4.35%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 4.35%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 4.35%, ICBC Credit Suisse GEM Index Investment Fund: 4.35%, Fullgoal CSI Tourism Thematic ETF: 4.35%, iPath CBOE S&P 500 BuyWrite Index ETN: 4.35%, MTEK ETF Leaders Tech: 4.35%, Hwabao WP CSI Old-Age Industry ETF: 4.35%, Penghua CSI 800 Securities and Insurance ETF: 4.35%, ICICI Prudential S&P BSE Liquid Rate ETF: 4.35%, Mirae Asset Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 4.35%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet CPI Linked 2023: 4.35%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet Non Linked 2023: 4.35%, Yuanta TPEx ESG Growth ETN: 4.35%, UBS ETC on UBS Bloomberg CMCI Agriculture TR Index CHF: 4.35%, HDFC Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 4.35%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 24 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 4.17%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 4.17%, BCC Global ETN: 4.17%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 4.17%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 4.17%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 4.17%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 4.17%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 4.17%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 4.17%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 4.17%, ICBC Credit Suisse GEM Index Investment Fund: 4.17%, Fullgoal CSI Tourism Thematic ETF: 4.17%, iPath CBOE S&P 500 BuyWrite Index ETN: 4.17%, MTEK ETF Leaders Tech: 4.17%, Hwabao WP CSI Old-Age Industry ETF: 4.17%, Penghua CSI 800 Securities and Insurance ETF: 4.17%, ICICI Prudential S&P BSE Liquid Rate ETF: 4.17%, Mirae Asset Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 4.17%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet CPI Linked 2023: 4.17%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet Non Linked 2023: 4.17%, Yuanta TPEx ESG Growth ETN: 4.17%, UBS ETC on UBS Bloomberg CMCI Agriculture TR Index CHF: 4.17%, HDFC Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 4.17%, GraniteShares 3x Short MicroStrategy Daily ETP: 4.17%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 25 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 4.00%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 4.00%, BCC Global ETN: 4.00%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 4.00%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 4.00%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 4.00%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 4.00%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 4.00%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 4.00%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 4.00%, ICBC Credit Suisse GEM Index Investment Fund: 4.00%, Fullgoal CSI Tourism Thematic ETF: 4.00%, iPath CBOE S&P 500 BuyWrite Index ETN: 4.00%, MTEK ETF Leaders Tech: 4.00%, Hwabao WP CSI Old-Age Industry ETF: 4.00%, Penghua CSI 800 Securities and Insurance ETF: 4.00%, ICICI Prudential S&P BSE Liquid Rate ETF: 4.00%, Mirae Asset Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 4.00%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet CPI Linked 2023: 4.00%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet Non Linked 2023: 4.00%, Yuanta TPEx ESG Growth ETN: 4.00%, UBS ETC on UBS Bloomberg CMCI Agriculture TR Index CHF: 4.00%, HDFC Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 4.00%, GraniteShares 3x Short MicroStrategy Daily ETP: 4.00%, Leverage Shares 3x Long Xpeng ETP Securities: 4.00%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 26 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 3.85%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 3.85%, BCC Global ETN: 3.85%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 3.85%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 3.85%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 3.85%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 3.85%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 3.85%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 3.85%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 3.85%, ICBC Credit Suisse GEM Index Investment Fund: 3.85%, Fullgoal CSI Tourism Thematic ETF: 3.85%, iPath CBOE S&P 500 BuyWrite Index ETN: 3.85%, MTEK ETF Leaders Tech: 3.85%, Hwabao WP CSI Old-Age Industry ETF: 3.85%, Penghua CSI 800 Securities and Insurance ETF: 3.85%, ICICI Prudential S&P BSE Liquid Rate ETF: 3.85%, Mirae Asset Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 3.85%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet CPI Linked 2023: 3.85%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet Non Linked 2023: 3.85%, Yuanta TPEx ESG Growth ETN: 3.85%, UBS ETC on UBS Bloomberg CMCI Agriculture TR Index CHF: 3.85%, HDFC Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 3.85%, GraniteShares 3x Short MicroStrategy Daily ETP: 3.85%, Leverage Shares 3x Long Xpeng ETP Securities: 3.85%, Leverage Shares 3x Long NIO ETP Securities: 3.85%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 27 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 3.70%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 3.70%, BCC Global ETN: 3.70%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 3.70%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 3.70%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 3.70%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 3.70%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 3.70%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 3.70%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 3.70%, ICBC Credit Suisse GEM Index Investment Fund: 3.70%, Fullgoal CSI Tourism Thematic ETF: 3.70%, iPath CBOE S&P 500 BuyWrite Index ETN: 3.70%, MTEK ETF Leaders Tech: 3.70%, Hwabao WP CSI Old-Age Industry ETF: 3.70%, Penghua CSI 800 Securities and Insurance ETF: 3.70%, ICICI Prudential S&P BSE Liquid Rate ETF: 3.70%, Mirae Asset Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 3.70%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet CPI Linked 2023: 3.70%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet Non Linked 2023: 3.70%, Yuanta TPEx ESG Growth ETN: 3.70%, UBS ETC on UBS Bloomberg CMCI Agriculture TR Index CHF: 3.70%, HDFC Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 3.70%, GraniteShares 3x Short MicroStrategy Daily ETP: 3.70%, Leverage Shares 3x Long Xpeng ETP Securities: 3.70%, Leverage Shares 3x Long NIO ETP Securities: 3.70%, Leverage Shares -3x Short Nvidia NVDA ETP Securities: 3.70%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 28 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 3.57%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 3.57%, BCC Global ETN: 3.57%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 3.57%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 3.57%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 3.57%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 3.57%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 3.57%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 3.57%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 3.57%, ICBC Credit Suisse GEM Index Investment Fund: 3.57%, Fullgoal CSI Tourism Thematic ETF: 3.57%, iPath CBOE S&P 500 BuyWrite Index ETN: 3.57%, MTEK ETF Leaders Tech: 3.57%, Hwabao WP CSI Old-Age Industry ETF: 3.57%, Penghua CSI 800 Securities and Insurance ETF: 3.57%, ICICI Prudential S&P BSE Liquid Rate ETF: 3.57%, Mirae Asset Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 3.57%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet CPI Linked 2023: 3.57%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet Non Linked 2023: 3.57%, Yuanta TPEx ESG Growth ETN: 3.57%, UBS ETC on UBS Bloomberg CMCI Agriculture TR Index CHF: 3.57%, HDFC Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 3.57%, GraniteShares 3x Short MicroStrategy Daily ETP: 3.57%, Leverage Shares 3x Long Xpeng ETP Securities: 3.57%, Leverage Shares 3x Long NIO ETP Securities: 3.57%, Leverage Shares -3x Short Nvidia NVDA ETP Securities: 3.57%, GraniteShares 3x Short NVIDIA Daily ETP: 3.57%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 29 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 3.45%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 3.45%, BCC Global ETN: 3.45%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 3.45%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 3.45%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 3.45%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 3.45%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 3.45%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 3.45%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 3.45%, ICBC Credit Suisse GEM Index Investment Fund: 3.45%, Fullgoal CSI Tourism Thematic ETF: 3.45%, iPath CBOE S&P 500 BuyWrite Index ETN: 3.45%, MTEK ETF Leaders Tech: 3.45%, Hwabao WP CSI Old-Age Industry ETF: 3.45%, Penghua CSI 800 Securities and Insurance ETF: 3.45%, ICICI Prudential S&P BSE Liquid Rate ETF: 3.45%, Mirae Asset Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 3.45%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet CPI Linked 2023: 3.45%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet Non Linked 2023: 3.45%, Yuanta TPEx ESG Growth ETN: 3.45%, UBS ETC on UBS Bloomberg CMCI Agriculture TR Index CHF: 3.45%, HDFC Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 3.45%, GraniteShares 3x Short MicroStrategy Daily ETP: 3.45%, Leverage Shares 3x Long Xpeng ETP Securities: 3.45%, Leverage Shares 3x Long NIO ETP Securities: 3.45%, Leverage Shares -3x Short Nvidia NVDA ETP Securities: 3.45%, GraniteShares 3x Short NVIDIA Daily ETP: 3.45%, GraniteShares 3x Long NIO Daily ETP: 3.45%, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Create a portfolio of 30 ETFs with equal weights?",
        "response": "Here is the list of suitable ETFs and their weightings:\nAmundi UK Government Bond 0-5Y UCITS ETF: 3.33%, Chimera S&P KSA Shariah ETF: 3.33%, BCC Global ETN: 3.33%, SBER Dynamic Smart Fund: 3.33%, E FundSI Hong Kong Securities Investment Theme ETF: 3.33%, Samsung KODEX Active Korea Total Bond Market AA- ETF: 3.33%, UBS ETC 2x Short CMCI WTI Crude Oil Index - 3 Month: 3.33%, Chimera S&P UAE Shariah ETF: 3.33%, AXA-SPDB CSI Intelligent Electric Vehicles ETF: 3.33%, Kotak NIFTY 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 3.33%, ICBC Credit Suisse GEM Index Investment Fund: 3.33%, Fullgoal CSI Tourism Thematic ETF: 3.33%, iPath CBOE S&P 500 BuyWrite Index ETN: 3.33%, MTEK ETF Leaders Tech: 3.33%, Hwabao WP CSI Old-Age Industry ETF: 3.33%, Penghua CSI 800 Securities and Insurance ETF: 3.33%, ICICI Prudential S&P BSE Liquid Rate ETF: 3.33%, Mirae Asset Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 3.33%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet CPI Linked 2023: 3.33%, KSM ETF 00 Index Bullet Non Linked 2023: 3.33%, Yuanta TPEx ESG Growth ETN: 3.33%, UBS ETC on UBS Bloomberg CMCI Agriculture TR Index CHF: 3.33%, HDFC Nifty 1D Rate Liquid ETF: 3.33%, GraniteShares 3x Short MicroStrategy Daily ETP: 3.33%, Leverage Shares 3x Long Xpeng ETP Securities: 3.33%, Leverage Shares 3x Long NIO ETP Securities: 3.33%, Leverage Shares -3x Short Nvidia NVDA ETP Securities: 3.33%, GraniteShares 3x Short NVIDIA Daily ETP: 3.33%, GraniteShares 3x Long NIO Daily ETP: 3.33%, Huatai-Pinebridge CSI Science and Technology Innovation Board 50 ETF: 3.33%, "
    }
]